anaxanet.com 2010-12-12

# Privacy Policy : ASP NET Windows Web Hosting by ASPnix

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how ASPnix collects information from all end users of ASPnix's Internet and web hosting services (the "Services") - those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who pay a service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Customers") - what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such information. ASPnix requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Introduction

ASPnix collects information in different ways from Visitors and Customers who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.

Registration

Customers are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, email address, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Customers during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for security and billing purposes). This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. ASPnix may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Customers provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Customers). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to further enhance our services.

Partners and Sponsors

Some ASPnix products and services are offered to Visitors and Customers in conjunction with a non-affiliated partner or sponsor. To provide Visitors and Customers some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. ASPnix will share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered.

Responses to Email Inquiries

When Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to ASPnix, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. ASPnix does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

Voluntary Customer Surveys

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other ASPnix customers to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

Special Cases

It is ASPnix's policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors of Customers. However, ASPnix may disclose personal information about Visitors or Customers, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect ASPnix and our Customers.

"Cookies" and How ASPnix Uses Them

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. ASPnix may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-ASPnix Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies.

Non-affiliated partner or sponsors may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

ASPnix recommends that children ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to ASPnix, or to anyone else online.

Public Forums

Please remember that any information you may disclose in public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

ASPnix's Commitment to Data Security

Services and Web sites we sponsor or host have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

Where to direct questions about ASPnix's Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact ASPnix at any time.

Revisions to This Policy

ASPnix reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Service and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner.

Revised January 7, 2007
